Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 29: Greenpoint, circa 1990 - circa 2010
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Greenpoint, circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    This folder includes photographs of West Street and India Street, Greenpoint Avenue and West Street, and McGuinness Boulevard and Eagle Street.
  - INT Artist loft, Greenpoint warehouse [Greenpoint Terminal Market], circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Paulie Gee's, 60 Greenpoint Avenue (between Franklin Street and West Street), circa 2010 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Series 30: Highland Park, 1997-2007
  Series 30: Highland Park includes photographs of a school and streets in the Highland Park neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - EXT Neighborhood, Fulton Street and Miller Avenue, Fulton Street and Warwick Street, Highland Park, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - INT School, P.S. 108 (The Sal Abbracciamento School), Arlington Avenue and Linwood Street, Highland Park, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Series 31: Kensington, 1990-2011
  Series 31: Kensington includes photographs of streets, a school, a recording studio, and a subway station in the Kensington neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - 603 8th Street, 1990 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - EXT Neighborhood: Ocean Parkway, McDonald Avenue, and Avenue C, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - EXT/INT Recording Studio, Systems Two Recording Studio, 117 Ditmas Avenue (between East 2nd Street and McDonald Avenue), 2004 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Ditmas Junior High School, I.S. 062, 700 Cortelyou Road (between East 7th Street and East 8th Street), circa 2007 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - EXT Black World, 680 Ocean Parkway, 2010 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - EXT Elevated subway platform, F train, McDonald Avenue at 18th Street, 2011 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Series 32: Marine Park, 2003-2011
  Series 32: Marine Park includes photographs of Floyd Bennett Field and streets in the Marine Park neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Floyd Bennett Field, 2003 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Marine Park, Neighborhood, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Series 33: Midwood, circa 1995 - circa 2010
  Series 33: Midwood includes photographs of apartments, parks, stores, a recording studio, a billiards hall, and streets in the Midwood neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Tuxedo Shop, Zeller Tuxedos, 947 Kings Highway, circa 1995 (Box 50, Folder 14)
  - INT/EXT Neighborhood Bar, Starlite Lounge, McDonald Avenue at Avenue J, circa 1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 1010 Dorchester Road, Apt. 2E (between Coney Island Avenue and Stratford Road), Midwood, circa 1995 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Midwood, McDonald Avenue and Avenue M, F train Avenue N stop, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Pool Hall, Collegiate Billiards, 2310 Nostrand Avenue, Flatbush, circa 2000 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - McDonald Avenue overview, Neck Road, Village Road, Avenue U, Avenue J, 2003 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - EXT/INT Recording Studio, Fastlane Studios, 1860 Flatbush Avenue (between Avenue K and East 38th Street), 2004 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - INT Warehouse, Midwood Lumber and Millwork Warehouse, 1122 Coney Island Avenue (between Avenue H and I), 2004 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Paul W. Kolbert Playground, Rachel Haber Cohen Playground, East 17th Street and Avenue L, Midwood, circa 2010 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Series 34: Mill Basin, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 34: Mill Basin includes photographs of a catering hall, bowling alley, and streets in the Mill Basin neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - El Caribe Catering Hall, Strickland Avenue, Mill Basin, circa 1990 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Gil Hodges Lanes, 6161 Strickland Avenue, Mill Basin, 1999 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Mill Basin, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Series 35: Park Slope, circa 1985 - 2011
  Series 35: Park Slope includes photographs of apartments, houses, restaurants, bars, stores, schools, and streets in the Park Slope neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - EXT/INT Gus's Apartment, 546 3rd Street, Park Slope, circa 1985 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Prospect Hall, Chateau Bleu, circa 1987 (Box 88, Folder 3)
  - Manhattan EXT, Plaza Cinema, 314 Flatbush Avenue, circa 1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Tuxedo Shop, Tuxedo Den, 317 9th Street at 5th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Diner, 5th Avenue Café, 432 5th Avenue, Park Slope, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Prospect Hall staircases, Chateau Bleu, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    This location was scouted for Goodfellas. This folder was categorized under Auditoriums, Meeting Rooms, Catering Halls, Modern.
  - EXT Gus's Apartment: 125 Prospect Park West, 120 Prospect Park West roof, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - 499 12th Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - 863 President Street between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Union Street between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - 510 8th Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 16)
  - 492 12th Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 19)
  - 545 11th Street (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 1990
  - 14th Regiment Armory, Park Slope Armory, circa 1990 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Grand Prospect Hall: 263 Prospect Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Prospect Hall Caterers [The Grand Prospect Hall], 263 Prospect Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - 158 St. John's Place (between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue), circa 1995 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Coffee shop, The Luna Park Ice Cream Bar and Java Joint, 249 5th Avenue, Park Slope, circa 1995 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - INT Gus's Apartment, Brownstone, 554 3rd Street, Park Slope, circa 1995 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Diner, Benny's Diner, 819 8th Avenue at 9th Street, Park Slope, circa 1995 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 350 Bergen Street, Apt. 2 (between 3rd Avenue and 4th Avenue), circa 1995 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - President Street between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue, circa 1995 (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - INT Laurel's Apartment, 882 Carroll Street (between 8th Avenue and Prospect Park West), Park Slope, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - INT/EXT Laurel's Apartment, 36 Montgomery Place between 8th Avenue and Prospect Park West, Park Slope, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Park Slope Armory, 1402 8th Avenue (between 14th Street and 15th Street), Park Slope, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Roach Garden #15: Brooklyn Bears Community Garden, Flatbush Avenue between Atlantic Avenue and Pacific Street, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Aquarium, pet store, 339 9th Street, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - 827 Carroll Street, Park Slope, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - 614 2nd Street, Park Slope, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - 473 13th Street, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - 526 8th Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), 1996 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 225 16th Street (between 5th Avenue and 6th Avenue), 2nd floor, Park Slope, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - INT Jason's Apartment Research, 706 Degraw Street, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - INT Wexler's, 108 8th Avenue (between President Street and Caroll Street), Park Slope, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - INT Apartment, 196 Berkeley Place (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 306 14th Street at 5th Avenue, Park Slope, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - INT Sheriff's apartment, 641 Baltic Street, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 647 Warren Street (between 4th Avenue and 5th Avenue), Apartment 1, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 645 Warren Street (between 4th Avenue and 5th Avenue), 1st floor, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - EXT Brooklyn street, Prospect Park West (between 5th Street and 6th Street), Park Slope, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - EXT Brooklyn street, 1st Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - EXT Brooklyn street, corner of Prospect Park West and 1st Street, Park Slope, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Mike and Tony's, 239 5th Avenue (between Carroll Street and President Street), circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Park Slope block, 7th Avenue between 1st Street and 2nd Street, circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - EXT Street, Montgomery Place, circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - 508 12th Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - 490 13th Street, circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - EXT 60 Montgomery Place, circa 2000 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Park Slope streets, circa 2000 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    This folder includes photographs of 626 6th Street.
  - 847 President Street (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), circa 2000 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Townhouse, 559 1st Street at Prospect Park West, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 857 Carroll Street (between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue), 2001 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - INT - EXT Townhouse, 128 Lincoln Place between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue, Park Slope, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Townhouse, 558 1st Street at 8th Avenue, Park Slope, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - EXT Brownstone, 7th Avenue and Sterling Place, Park Slope, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 558 1st Street between 8th Avenue and Prospect Park West, Park Slope, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - 262 Garfield Place between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue, Park Slope, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Townhouse, 128 Lincoln Place between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - INT / EXT Brownstone, 553 2nd Street (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), 2001 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - View of 240 Berkeley Place (Rear), 913 Union Street, 2nd Floor balcony, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Fruit Stand, 79 7th Avenue between Berkeley Place and Union Street, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Copy Shop, Park Slope Copy Center, 123 7th Avenue between Carroll Street and President Street, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - View of backyard behind 240 Berkeley Place, 64 8th Avenue, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - EXT Electronics Store, Proline, 255 4th Avenue at Carroll Street, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Park Slope Ale House, 6th Avenue at 4th Street, 356 6th Avenue, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - 240 [Berkeley Place] details, 2002 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 138 St. Johns Place (between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue), 2002 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - EXT Fruit Stand: Y+B [Fruit Market], 80 7th Ave between Berkeley Place and Union Street, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - EXT Electronics store [Music Emporium, 286 Flatbush], 2002 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - EXT Pharmacy: Palma Chemists, 159 7th Avenue, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - EXT 7th Avenue (at Garfield Place), Park Slope, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Food Market: Tai's Market, 154 7th Avenue at Garfield Place, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Hardware store, Tarzian Hardware, 7th Avenue at 2nd Street, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 16)
  - INT/EXT Grocery store: Back to the Land, 142 7th Avenue between Carroll Street and Garfield Place, 2002 (Box 50, Folder 17)
  - INT/EXT Food market: Daniel's Food Market Inc., 147 7th Avenue between Garfield Place and Carroll Street, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - INT Bathroom/Various, Grand Prospect Hall, 263 Prospect Avenue between 5th Avenue and 6th Avenue, 2002 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Rooftop, 64 8th Avenue (between Berkeley Place and Union Street), Park Slope, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - View of Berkeley Place, 64 8th Avenue, 2002 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT The Montauk Club, 25 8th Avenue (between St. Johns Place and Lincoln Place), 2003 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone, Park Slope, 206 St. Johns Place (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), 2003 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - EXT Apartment Building, Park Slope, 35 Prospect Park West (between Montgomery Place and Garfield Place), 2003 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - 47 Plaza Street West (between Grand Army Plaza and Union Street), Park Slope, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - EXT Apartment Building, Park Slope, 140 8th Avenue at Montgomery Place, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - EXT Apartment Building, Park Slope, 9 Prospect Park West (between President Street and Carroll Street), 2003 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - EXT Apartment Building, Park Slope, 70 Prospect Park West, between 2nd Street and 3rd Street, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Park Slope neighborhood, 2003 (Box 59, Folder 10)
    This folder includes photographs of mostly unidentified streets, 7th Avenue and 15th Street, and Cafe Steinhof at 422 7th Avenue.
  - EXT Street - Park Slope: 5th Street between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue, 2003 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Afric Beauté, 82 6th Avenue at St. Marks Place, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Roof, 64 8th Avenue (between Berkeley Place and Union Street), Park Slope, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - EXT Hardware store [Tarzian Hardware, 193 7th Avenue], circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - EXT Townhouse, Brooklyn Conservatory of Music, 58 7th Avenue at Lincoln Place, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - EXT Brownstone, 276 Berkeley Place at Plaza Street West, Park Slope, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - EXT Backyard, Next to 240 Berkeley Place, 60 - 62 8th Avenue (between Berkeley Place and Union Street), Park Slope, circa 2005 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - INT/EXT Newsstand, Park Slope, 3rd Street Grocery and Newsstand, 206 7th Avenue between 2nd and 3rd Street, circa 2005 (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Roof, 60-62 8th Avenue (between Berkeley Place and Union Street), Park Slope, circa 2005 (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Roof, co-op, 220 Berkeley Place (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 2005 (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - 276 Berkeley Place, circa 2005 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - EXT Park Slope block, 7th Avenue between 2nd Street and 3rd Street, circa 2005 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - EXT Park Slope blocks, 7th Avenue between 3rd Street and 4th Street, circa 2005 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - EXT Park Slope blocks, 7th Avenue between 4th Street and 5th Street, circa 2005 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Catering space auditorium, St. Augustine Church [St. Francis Xavier's School], circa 2005 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Seedy rock club, Southpaw, 125 5th Avenue at Sterling Place, Park Slope, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - 62 8th Avenue, Backyard, Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Brownstone details, 70 8th Avenue at Union Street, Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - View of the backyard behind 240 Berkeley [Place], 913 Union Street, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - Hallways, P.S. 39, 417 6th Avenue (between 7th Street and 8th Street), circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - EXT Backyard, 240 Berkeley Place, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - EXT Brownstone, 240 Berkeley Place (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - [240 Berkeley Place], circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - INT Front windows, 240 Berkeley Place, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - EXT Brownstone, 240 Berkeley Place (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - 240 Berkeley Place, Interior halls, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - 58 8th Avenue, Backyard, Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - EXT Backyard, Next to 240 Berkeley Place, 56 8th Avenue at Berkeley Place, Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - EXT 240 Berkeley Place, circa 2010 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - 240 Berkeley Place EXT, circa 2010 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Views from 240 Berkeley Place, circa 2010 (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - EXT Berkeley Place, Street shots, circa 2010
  - EXT Brownstone, 240 Berkeley Place (between 7th Avenue and 8th Avenue), Park Slope, circa 2010 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Diner/Coffee Shop/Meeting Spot, Purity Diner, 289 7th Avenue (at 7th Street), Park Slope, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 396 6th Street (between 5th Avenue and 6th Avenue), Park Slope, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 440 6th Street, Park Slope, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 432 7th Street (between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue), 2010 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - INT/EXT Estate, 416 7th Street (between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue), Park Slope, 2010 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - INT/EXT carriage house, 152 Berkeley Place (between 6th Avenue and 7th Avenue), Park Slope, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Various Blacks, 225 6th Avenue, St. Francis Xavier Parish House, Park Slope, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 262 Garfield Place (between 8th Avenue and Fiske Place), Park Slope, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT townhouse, 631 2nd Street (between 8th Avenue and Prospect Park West), Park Slope, 2011 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT townhouse, 117 6th Avenue at Park Place (Park Slope), 2011 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 276 Berkeley Place (between 8th Avenue and Plaza Street West), Park Slope, 2011 (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 617 3rd Street between Prospect Park West and 8th Avenue, Park Slope, 2011 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT townhouse, 625 3rd Street (between 8th Avenue and Prospect Park West), Park Slope, 2011 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- Series 36: Prospect Heights, 1995-2011
  Series 36: Prospect Heights includes photographs of restaurants, bars, churches, Brooklyn Museum, Brooklyn Botanic Garden, Central Library of the Brooklyn Public Library, schools, churches, and a police precinct in the Prospect Heights neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Japanese Garden [Brooklyn Botanic Garden], 1995 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - The New Theatre of Brooklyn, 465 Dean Street, circa 1995 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - EXT Pet Shop: 628 Vanderbilt Avenue [ACME Pet Food, Inc.], 1996 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - EXT Brooklyn street, bank, or court, Brooklyn Public Library [Central Library], Grand Army Plaza, Eastern Parkway and Flatbush Avenue, 2000 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - EXT Irish pub, Mooney's Pub, 353 Flatbush Avenue, (between Sterling Place and Carlton Place), circa 2000 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Former Daily News building, 700 Pacific Street, circa 2000 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - INT Party, Brooklyn Museum, 200 Eastern Parkway, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Carlton Avenue at St. Marks Place, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Grace Island Cuisine, 685 Washington Avenue, between Prospect Place and St. Marks Avenue, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Police precinct, 77th Police Precinct Annex, 653 Grand Avenue at Park Place (off Washington Avenue), 2004 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Tom's Restaurant, 782 Washington Avenue, corner of Sterling Place, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - INT Museum / Event space, Brooklyn Museum, 200 Eastern Parkway, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT School, P.S. 340 North Star Academy, 227 Sterling Place at Vanderbilt Avenue, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - EXT Church, The Duryea Presbyterian Church, 362 Sterling Place at Underhill Avenue, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - INT Science museum, Brooklyn Botanic Garden, 1000 Washington Avenue, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 214 Park Place, Apt. 1, 2010 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone - Abby Black, 83 St. Mark's Avenue between Carlton Avenue and Flatbush Avenue, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT House - Abby Black, 326 Park Place (between Underhill Avenue and Vanderbilt Avenue), Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone - Abby Black, 95 St. Marks Avenue between Carlton Avenue and Flatbush Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone - Abby Black, 121 St. Marks Avenue between Flatbush Avenue and Carlton Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse - Abby Black, 120 St. Marks Avenue, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - I/E Brownstone - Abby Black, 132 St. Marks Avenue between Carlton Avenue and Flatbush Avenue, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone, 415 Sterling Place between Underhill Avenue and Washington Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone, 284 Park Place between Vanderbilt Avenue and Underhill Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone, 327 Park Place between Underhill Avenue and Vanderbilt Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse/Brownstone - Abby Black, 151 Prospect Place at Carlton Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Brownstone, 147 Prospect Place at Carlton Avenue, Prospect Heights, 2011 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Series 37: Prospect Park, 1992 - circa 2010
  Series 37: Prospect Park includes photographs of playgrounds, structures, and paths in Prospect Park in Brooklyn.
  - EXT Long Meadow, Prospect Park and Grand Army Plaza Arch [Soldiers and Sailors Memorial Arch], 1992 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Prospect Park, 1994 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - EXT Reservoir, Prospect Park Boathouse, 1995 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Boat House, Prospect Park, circa 1995 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Third Street Playground, Prospect Park, at 3rd Street, circa 1995 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Prospect Park, 1996 (Box 44, Folder 33)
    This folder includes photographs of the Prospect Park Boathouse and Lullwater Bridge, Terrace Bridge, Prospect Lake.
  - The Tennis House, Prospect Park, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Prospect Park, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Prospect Park, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Prospect Park arches, 1998 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    This folder includes photographs of Cleft Ridge Span, Nethermead Arches, Endale Arch, Meadowport Arch.
  - Prospect Park, Playground Three, Prospect Park West at 3rd Street, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - EXT Playground, Prospect Park, Lincoln Playground, Ocean Avenue at Lincoln Road, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - EXT Prospect Park, Prospect Park West (North of 3rd Street), 2003 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - EXT Playground, Prospect Park, Imagination Playground, Ocean Avenue, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - EXT Prospect Park, 2003 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Villa, Prospect Park [Litchfield Villa], 2003 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Prospect Park and environs, 2007 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    This folder includes photographs of the Parade Ground soccer field, Prospect Park Lake, Prospect Park Wildlife Center, Lefferts Historic House, and Grand Army Plaza. This folder was categorized under "Restaurants, Parks, Housing Projects, Hospitals, Apt. Towers, Retirement Homes."
  - Harmony Playground, Prospect Park West at 11th Street, circa 2010 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Series 38: Red Hook, circa 1990 - 2011
  Series 38: Red Hook includes photographs of bars, public housing, manufacturing and industrial areas, apartments, and streets in the Red Hook neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - INT Bar, John's Bar, Red Hook [Sunny's Bar], circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Van Brunt Street and Commerce Street, Red Hook (Night), circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Brooklyn Battery, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Van Dyke Street and Ferris Street, Red Hook, bottling plant, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Revere Sugar, Van Dyke warehouses, Van Dyke Street and Richards Street, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Pier 41, Red Hook, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Red Hook Housing [Red Hook Houses], Henry Street and Lorraine Street, Red Hook, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Red Hook Housing [Red Hook Houses], Clinton Street and Centre Street, Red Hook, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Brooklyn Battery Tunnel - electrical room, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Various streets, Red Hook, circa 1990 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    This folder includes photographs of Continental Terminals, Inc., Redhook Holiness Church, Beard Street, Coffey Street, Richards Street, and T. I. Buron Grocery.
  - Red Hook Container Yard, Red Hook, circa 1990 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Dock warehouse, Port Authority Red Hook Terminal, circa 1990 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - New York Shipyard, 1 Beard Street, Red Hook, circa 1990 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Van Brunt Street and Commerce Street, Red Hook, circa 1992 (Box 41, Folder 11)